https://www.crossculture.com/privacy-policy/

twitter
linkedin
About UsThe Lewis ModelLinear-activeMulti-activeReactiveFacts and FiguresOur TeamOur Founder Richard LewisTrainers and PartnersTrainers and PartnersFeatured PartnersOur ServicesConsultancyTraining and CoachingCulture Specific SeminarsFunctional SeminarsKeynote SpeechesCoachingTake-awaysTools and PublicationsCultureActiveCross-Cultural Dialogue MatMapsBooksArticlesClient StoriesIn FocusLatest NewsBlogContact UsCookies & Privacy PolicyTerms and Conditions
About UsThe Lewis ModelLinear-activeMulti-activeReactiveFacts and FiguresOur TeamOur Founder Richard LewisTrainers and PartnersTrainers and PartnersFeatured PartnersOur ServicesConsultancyTraining and CoachingCulture Specific SeminarsFunctional SeminarsKeynote SpeechesCoachingTake-awaysTools and PublicationsCultureActiveCross-Cultural Dialogue MatMapsBooksArticlesClient StoriesIn FocusLatest NewsBlogContact Us
go‘(In) twenty years I have never previously had an experience of such professionalism, expert competence and service orientation’Cookies & Privacy Policy
Home / Cookies & Privacy PolicyPrivacyAt Cross Culture, we’re committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.This Policy explains when and why we collect personal information about people who visit our website, how we use it, the conditions under which we may disclose it to others and how we keep it secure.We may change this Policy from time to time so please check this page occasionally to ensure that you’re happy with any changes. By using our website, you’re agreeing to be bound by this Policy.Who are weWe’re Richard Lewis Communications Ltd a registered company (no. 02450981). The registered address is Riversdown House, Warnford, SO32 3LH, UK.How do we collect information from you?We obtain information about you when you use our website, for example, when you contact us about our services via our form on our contact page, make a purchase or create an account on our website.What type of information is collected from you?The personal information we collect might include your name, email address, address, phone number and your IP address. We also collect information regarding what pages are accessed and when but we are unable to link this to you personally.How is your information used?We may use your information to:to respond to you when you email us;to carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into by you and us;seek your views or comments on the services we provide;notify you of changes to our services;send you communications which you have requested or that may be of interest to you. These may include news about what we have been up to;process an order.We review our retention periods for personal information on a regular basis. We will hold your personal information on our systems for as long as is necessary for the relevant activity, or as long as is set out in any relevant contract you hold with us.We will only contact you for marketing purposes by email if you have signed up for our newsletters.All emails sent via the contact forms on our site as saved to the our websites logs and also all communications are sent directly from the site to us via traditional email which only authorized staff have access to these.The only other data stored in our websites logs are IP addresses but that piece of information does not directly identify a person as we collected no other data alongside it. Plus we have no legal means of obtaining suffcient additional data to make such a link – therefore an IP address on it’s own is not classed as personal data and thus is not covered by GDPR.Who has access to your information?Only Cross Culture and our Consultants will have access to your information you send us directly. We will not sell or rent your information to third parties. We will not share your information with third parties for any purposes including marketing.If you leave a comment on our site, the information you provide will be passed though a third party to check if it is spam or not.Your choicesYou have a choice about whether or not you wish to receive information from us. If you do not want to receive direct marketing communications from us about the services we o er, then you can opt-out of these communications by using the links in all communications to update your preferences. Or alternatively you can contact us by email: michael.gates@ rlcglobal.com or telephone on +44 (0)1962 77 11 11.How you can access and update your informationThe accuracy of your information is important to us. If you change email address, or any of the other information we hold is inaccurate or out of date, you can edit this information by logging into your store account (link in the footer of the site) and going to the Account Details and Addresses pages. Or alternatively you can contact us by email: michael.gates@rlcglobal. com or telephone on +44 (0)1962 77 11 11 . You also have the right to ask for a copy of the information Cross Culture hold about you.Security precautions in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of your informationWhen you give us personal information, we take steps to ensure that it’s treated securely. Any information is encrypted and protected with the following software 128 Bit encryption on SSL. When you are on a secure page, a lock icon will appear in your web browser, meaning the connection between you and the server is secure.Non-sensitive details (sent via email forms) are transmitted normally over the Internet, and this can never be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your information, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems.Links to other websitesOur website may contain links to other websites run by other organisations. This privacy policy applies only to our website‚ so we encourage you to read the privacy statements on the other websites you visit. We cannot be responsible for the privacy policies and practices of other sites even if you access them using links from our website.In addition, if you linked to our website from a third party site, we cannot be responsible for the privacy policies and practices of the owners and operators of that third party site and recommend that you check the policy of that third party site.CookiesLike many other websites, the Cross culture website uses cookies. ‘Cookies’ are small pieces of information sent by an organisation to your computer and stored on your hard drive to allow that website to recognise you when you visit. They collect statistical data about your browsing actions and patterns and do not identify you as an individual. This helps us to improve our website and deliver a better more personalised service.Most web browsers allow some control of most cookies through the browser settings. However, please note that if you choose to disable cookies, then parts of this website may not function correctly.By using and browsing the Cross Culture website, you consent to cookies being used in accordance with this policy. If you do not consent, you must turn off cookies or refrain from using the site, and all performance cookies will not be activated.What cookies do Cross Culture use?Broadly, there are 2 types of cookie we use:Strictly necessary cookies. These are cookies that are essential to make a website work and enable features that users have speciffcally asked for. These types of cookies are commonly used with shopping baskets or e-billing. Without use of cookies, these features of the website could not operate.Performance cookies. These cookies collect anonymous information about users for the purpose of assessing the performance of a website. Common uses include well-known web analytics tools such as ‘Google Analytics’.The table below list the cookies we use and will set regardless of your acceptance of our cookie message, these cookies are seen as essential to the running of the website, without them, desktop, mobile and tablet devices will not display the images properly.Strictly necessary cookies Cookie NameDescriptionUsed forcookie_notice_acceptedRemembers if you accepted cookies or notsix monthscomment_author
comment_author_email
comment_author_urlIf you leave a comment on the website e.g. on a page, article or blog post, then a cookie may be stored to ‘remember’ your email address for the next time you post (should you choose the “remember me” option). All cookies starting with comment_author deal with thiswordfence_ver edHuman
wfvt_[hash]
wfwaf-authcookie-[hash]A security and firewall plugin. Helps in the prevention of the site being hacked.1 daywoocommerce_cart_hash
woocommerce_items_in_cart wp_woocommerce_session_[hash]Deal with the eCommerce parts of the website1 day
1 day
3 dayswordpress_logged_in_[hash]
wordpress_sec_[hash]Remembers that you have logged in to the site1 day
1 dayPerformance cookies:Cookie NameDescriptionUsed for__ga
__gidWe use Google Analytics to allow us to analyse the traffic to our site and to review a number of statistics regarding our visitors. (Further information on the data they collect is available here).2 years
1 dayReview of this PolicyWe keep this Policy under regular review. This Policy was last updated in June 2018.We deliver embedded knowledge of cultural behaviours for better global businessCookies & Privacy PolicyTerms and ConditionsMy AccountStaff Admin LoginPart of the Richard Lewis Communications Group © 2020 | WordPress Web Development by CuCo
We use cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website. If you continue to use this site we will assume that you are happy with it.OkNoPrivacy policy
